ageofwushu.com 2013-05-18

# Age of Wushu : Free To Play MMORPG - Coming Soon

**Privacy Policy**

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy governs your use of the web sites published and maintained by Snail Games USA, Inc. ("Snail USA," "we," "us," or "our,") including [www.snailgamesusa.com](http://www.snailgamesusa.com/) or other affiliate sites (collectively, the "Web Site"). By visiting this Web Site, and/or using the services offered on or through this Web Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as they may be amended from time to time. As we update and expand our Web Site, this Privacy Policy may change. Snail USA encourages you to review this page from time to time. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and made part of, the Snail USA Web Site Terms of Use, which governs your use of this Web Site in general.

**Summary**

It is Snail USA’s policy to respect and protect the privacy of visitors to this Web Site. Accordingly, Snail USA does not extract, without permission, Personal Information (as defined below) about its visitors or their computer at any time while on Snail USA’s Web Site, except for Personal Information that is actively provided by such visitors through registration, logging in and out, online forms or other means. Snail USA will, however, analyze information about our visitors as a group to make our Web Site better, but visitors are not individually identified when we do this.

When dealing with children who we have actual knowledge are under the age of 13, Snail USA follows stringent guidelines that prohibit the sharing of Personal Information with any third parties, except in limited circumstances such as our service providers who use such information on our behalf. Our privacy policies regarding children are outlined in Snail USA’s Parental Consent Policy section below.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you may provide to us, or that we may obtain, through sources other than our Web Site, such as by phone, mail and other live and print mediums.

This Privacy Policy shall be interpreted under the laws of the United States, regardless of the location of individual users.

You have the right to opt out of certain uses and disclosures of your Personal Information. See the Right to Opt Out section below for further details.

**California Privacy Rights**

The following applies to California residents who have an established business relationship with Snail USA. If we collect Personal Information from you we will not share your Personal Information with any third parties unless required to do so by operation of law or in order to prevent harm to you or any other users of our Web Site. For more information on how your Personal Information is collected, used and shared, please read the remainder of this Privacy Policy.   

**What Snail USA Collects**

Snail USA may collect a variety of statistical data about its Web Site visitors. This data includes the source IP address (as further described below in the "IP Address and Clickstream Data" section) of the visitor, the time of visit, the areas of the site visited and information about browser, operating system and other system parameters. As of the date of this Privacy Policy, none of this information is used to personally identify any individual visitor, and is used solely for the purposes of analyzing overall traffic and usage patterns. However, Snail USA reserves the right to begin matching such usage data with an individual’s Personal Information subsequent to the date of this Privacy Policy.

In order to make your visits to our Web Site and use of the services available on or through our Web Site as worthwhile as possible, Snail USA may also collect Personal Information about its visitors, but only when a visitor provides such Personal Information to us in the process of entering contests or sweepstakes, signing up for our newsletter(s), using our "Feedback" feature, registering with the Web Site or using other services available on or through our Web Site. The information that you give us and information about your order, purchases or other activities on the Web Site may be combined with other Personal Information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) available from our records and other sources. "Personal Information" includes usernames, e-mail addresses, wireless addresses, credit card and other payment information, purchase history, demographic information, and/or other information that may identify you as an individual or allow online or offline contact with you as an individual. This information is used by Snail USA to fulfill your requests and for marketing and research purposes. This information will not be shared with other marketers to bring you offers of interest. Certain areas of Snail USA’s Web Site may require user registration in order to gain access; once you register with the Snail USA Web Site to use that content, you will no longer be anonymous to us.   

**Right to Opt Out**

You have the right to opt out of certain of our uses of your Personal Information. For example, at the time you are requested to provide Personal Information on this Web Site, you may have the opportunity to elect to, or not to receive correspondence from us. You may make this request by sending an e-mail to [_support@snailgamesusa.com_](mailto:support@snailgamesusa.com) or by electing to not receive our e-mail newsletter notifications during your registration process. Furthermore, all of our correspondence will include a link to Opt Out of future newsletters and/or notifications. In this e-mail, please say whether: (i) you would like to opt out of receiving promotional correspondence from Snail USA in general, or just via e-mail, postal mail, short message service (SMS), instant messaging, and/or by phone, and/or (ii) you would only like to opt out of certain of Snail USA’s e-newsletters or correspondence, and if so which ones. You may also opt out of Snail USA’s promotional e-mails by clicking on an opt-out link within the e-mail you receive.

Please understand that if you opt out of receiving correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and communications with us.   

**Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Snail USA may use "cookie" technology to enhance a visitor's online experience by making it easier to navigate through our Web Site or to make an activity work better.

Cookies are small pieces of information or data files that are sent through your browser or related software from a Web server and are stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies may be used to track where you travel on our Web Site and what you look at and purchase, and they allow a computer to "remember" information from our Web Site for future use. The use of cookies is an industry standard and is practiced by most major Web sites. Cookies alone tell us nothing about who you are, but they may enable us to relate your use of our Web Site to other information, including your Personal Information, which you have provided to us when you registered for notification about one of our products or purchased a product from us by visiting our Web Site. All of these purposes serve to enhance your experience while using our services in the ways described below.

Most Web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. Additionally, if you have a Flash player installed on your computer, your Flash player can be set to reject or delete Flash cookies. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, the Web Site or certain areas or features of the Web Site.

Snail USA also may use "clear GIFs" (aka "Web beacons" or "pixel tags") or similar technologies, in the Web Site and/or in our communications with you to enable us to know whether you have visited a web page or received a message. A clear GIF is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located on a web page or in an e-mail or other type of message, which is retrieved from a remote site on the Internet enabling the verification of an individual’s viewing or receipt of a web page or message. A clear gif may enable us to relate your viewing or receipt of a web page or message to other information about you, including your Personal Information.

We may use cookies and other tracking technologies in a variety of ways, including:

  * Keeping count of return visits to our Web Site or our advertisers’ or partners’ sites
  * Accumulating and reporting anonymous, aggregate (data collected in mass), statistical information on website and advertisement usage 
  * Determining which features our customers like best   

**IP Address and “Clickstream” Data**

Our server automatically collects data about your server’s Internet address when you visit us. This information, known as an Internet Protocol address, or IP Address, is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you’re on the Internet. When you request pages from our Web Site, our servers may log your IP Address and sometimes your domain name. Our server may also record the referring page that linked you to us (e.g., another Web site or a search engine); the pages you visit on this Web Site; the Web site you visit after this Web Site; the ads you see and/or click on; other information about the type of Web browser, computer, platform, related software and settings you are using; any search terms you have entered on this Web Site or a referral site; and other Web usage activity and data logged by our Web servers. We use this information for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web Site. Such information may also be used to gather broad demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service Provider. We reserve the right to link this information with your Personal Information.

Any or all of these activities with regard to Web site usage information (i.e., information gathered through the use of cookies, Web bugs and clickstream data) may be performed on our behalf by our services providers.   

**How Snail USA Uses Personal Information**

Personal Information is used to enhance and custom-tailor each user's experience on the Web Site. Such information will also be used, for example, to process your orders, respond to your requests and inquiries and provide you with the services and features offered on or through our Web Site.

Snail USA may also use Personal Information to maintain our internal record keeping. We reserve the right to match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including both Personal Information and Web Site usage information, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources. In addition, we may send you notices (for example, in the form of e-mails, mailings, and the like), and otherwise correspond with you, about products, services, companies and events, sponsored by us and others, that we think might interest you. You may opt-out of receiving such notices from us by following the instructions in the Right to Opt Out section above.

In addition, Snail USA may use Personal Information to generate aggregate data about our Web Site’s visitors.   

**Requests For Feedback**

Snail USA may request feedback from visitors to the Web Site regarding an activity or piece of content on the Web Site. Such feedback is used for internal purposes only.   

**How Snail USA Shares Information Collected Online**

Snail USA will not sell, rent or give a visitor's Personal Information to any third party unless required to do so by operation of the law or in order to protect the users of the Web Site or in the limited circumstances required in order to correct an error regarding a players account; in such case, Snail USA will only share as much information as is necessary and only with its parent or affiliated partners in order to remedy any errors. Notwithstanding the above, Snail USA may, however, share aggregate information about users of our Web Site, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not describe or identify any individual user, with our advertisers, business partners, sponsors and certain others, as further described herein. As mentioned above, this aggregate information is used to develop, improve and customize Snail USA’s Web Site to better serve visitors to our Web Site.

.   

**Co-sponsored Contests, Sweepstakes and Offerings**

Some of our contests, sweepstakes and other offerings may be co-sponsored by another company. In those situations, we may share the information we obtain from you in connection with such contest, sweepstake or offering with our co-sponsor, unless you instruct us not to by following the instructions in the Right to Opt Out section above. In those situations, our co-sponsors will have the right to use your information for their own purposes, in accordance with their own policies. We are not responsible for how our co-sponsors may use your information.   

**Service Providers**

We may use third party partners to help operate our Web Site and deliver our products and services, and may share your information with our affiliates, service providers and other third parties that provide products or services for or through this Web Site or for our business (such as Web site or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf).   

**Legally Compelled Disclosures**

We may disclose user information to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, at our discretion, or otherwise as required or permitted by law, including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas. We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of the Web Site, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We may also report information about your account to credit bureaus. Late payments, missed payments, or other defaults on your account may be reflected in your credit report.   

**Business Transfer**

In the event that Snail USA, or substantially all of its assets, is acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, Personal Information may be one of the transferred assets.   

**Wireless Addresses**

If the e-mail address you provide to us is a wireless e-mail address, you agree to receive messages at such address from Snail USA. You understand that your wireless carrier's standard or premium rates apply to these messages, and that you may change your mind at any time by following the instructions in the Right to Opt Out section above. You represent that you are the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges.   

**Advertisers and Third Party "Linked-To" Web Sites**

Snail USA may include advertisements and/or links to web sites operated by third parties that are not sponsors and are not affiliated with Snail USA. Snail USA tries to make sure that when there are links off the Web Site, they are working and lead visitors to interesting, fun and informative areas. However, it is hard to guarantee what exactly is presented on other Web sites or where links elsewhere may lead. Snail USA is not responsible for the content, practices, or information provided or requested on Web sites operated by third parties. Further, advertisements on and links to or from [snailgamesusa.com](http://snailgamesusa.com/) do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement, or approval by Snail USA of the content, policies, practices or products or services offered on these Web sites.

Parents/guardians should check each Web site's privacy policy and terms of use in order to understand their policies and practices regarding the collection and use of personally identifiable information. Snail USA also suggests that parents/guardians review the privacy policies of all Web sites that their children visit, including those Web sites linking to or from the Snail USA Web Site. Information provided to those web sites will be subject to the privacy policy posted at that web site.   

**Security**

The importance of security for all Personal Information associated with visitors to our Web Site is of utmost concern to us. Snail USA exercises great care and implements a variety of technologies in an effort to help make the Snail USA Web Site secure against unauthorized access and to protect the Personal Information visitors choose to provide to us. Snail USA periodically reviews and updates these measures. Unfortunately, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be secure, and Snail USA cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers. As a result, while Snail USA strives to protect a visitor's Personal Information, Snail USA cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us or from our online products or services, and a visitor does so at his/her own risk. Snail USA uses the industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption when credit card information is transmitted to us.

If you contact us by e-mail or a "contact us" or similar feature on our Web site, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. A third party could view information you send by these methods in transit.

We will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission.

In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your Personal Information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail. You consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification. If you prefer for us to use another method to notify you in this situation, please e-mail us at [support@snailgamesusa.com](mailto:support@snailgamesusa.com) with the alternative contact information you wish to be used.   

**Review and deletion of personal information**

You may review and delete the Personal Information about you that is contained in your user account at Snail USA at any time. If you would like to review or delete this information, please contact us at:   

**Snail Games USA, Inc.**

Privacy Review

PO Box 13039

Marina Del Rey, CA 90295   

or send an email to [_support@snailgamesusa.com_](mailto:support@snailgamesusa.com). 

**Phishing**

With identity theft a continuing problem, it has become increasingly common for unauthorized individuals to send e-mail messages to consumers, purporting to represent a legitimate company such as a bank or on-line merchant, requesting that the consumer provide personal, often sensitive information. Sometimes, the domain name of the e-mail address from which the e-mail appears to have been sent, and the domain name of the web site requesting such information, appears to be the domain name of a legitimate, trusted company. In reality, such sensitive information is received by an unauthorized individual to be used for purposes of identity theft. This illegal activity has come to be known as "phishing."

If you receive an e-mail or other correspondence requesting that you provide any sensitive information (including your Web Site password or credit card information) via e-mail or to a Web site that does not seem to be affiliated with our Web Site, or that otherwise seems suspicious to you, please do not provide such information, and report such request to us at [support@snailgamesusa.com](mailto:support@snailgamesusa.com).   

**Consent to Processing**

By providing Personal Information to this Web Site, you understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other countries and territories.   

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Snail Games USA reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any other of our policies or practices, at any time, and will notify users of this Web Site by posting such changed or updated Privacy Policy on this page. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to this Web Site. Under certain circumstances, we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our Privacy Policy by additional means, such as posting a notice on the front page of our Web Site to sending you an e-mail.   

**Questions, Concerns and Comments**

If you have any questions regarding Snail USA’s Privacy Policy, please contact us at [_support@snailgamesusa.com_](mailto:support@snailgamesusa.com) or write to us at: 

**Snail Games USA, Inc.**

Business & Legal Affairs

PO Box 13039

Marina Del Rey, CA 90295   

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**

Never provide any information about yourself on the Internet without your parent's/guardian's permission. Please read Snail USA’s Parental Consent Policy (see below) with your parents/guardians before you go any further. Where legally required, Snail USA requires your parent’s/guardian’s written (or electronic) permission for children who we have actual knowledge are under age thirteen (13) to provide us with certain Personal Information required to get any Snail USA newsletter(s), order subscriptions, enter any clubs, etc., or participate in other activities and/or services available on or through the Web Site.   

**SNAIL USA’S PARENTAL CONSENT POLICY**

Where Snail USA’s information collection activities involve children that Snail USA has actual knowledge are under the age of thirteen (13), Snail USA provides special privacy protections. In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"), Snail USA will not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of thirteen (13) without first obtaining parental consent or otherwise following the requirements set forth by COPPA. Furthermore, Snail USA does not share any Personal Information that Snail USA has actual knowledge is about users under the age of thirteen (13) with third parties.

Prior to providing any Personal Information (such as your name, e-mail address, address, phone number etc.) either by placing an order for merchandise, entering a contest or sweepstakes (if eligible), or participating in any other activity offered through the Web Site, where legally required, children who Snail USA has actual knowledge are under the age of thirteen (13) must have a parent provide an express confirmation of parental consent by sending an e-mail to [support@snailgamesusa.com](mailto:support@snailgamesusa.com). In these instances, users who Snail USA has actual knowledge are under the age of thirteen (13) are prompted for a parent's e-mail address. This e-mail address will be sent a notification message with an embedded link to a parental consent page on the Snail USA Web Site. The child's registration, order, transaction or request will be considered incomplete until the child's parent uses this link to complete the parental consent process.

Alternatively, parents may send a written Parental Consent letter to:

**Snail Games USA, Inc.**

Parental Consent

PO Box 13039

Marina Del Rey, CA 90295   

The Consent letter must state that the child's "Parent" or "Legal Guardian," by his or her signature, consents to the collection of the child's Personal Information. Consent may be revoked by sending a Parental Consent Revocation letter and sending it to the address or fax number above. Please note that if a parent does not permit Snail USA’s use or collection of Personal Information or has instructed Snail USA to delete personally identifiable information, a child's participation in those Web Site activities for which the Personal Information has been requested may not be possible.

In compliance with COPPA, Snail USA is sensitive about children consulting with parents or guardians before furnishing Personal Information or ordering anything online. Snail USA encourages parents/guardians to supervise and join their children in exploring cyberspace.

With the limited exceptions described in this Privacy Policy, Snail USA will not disclose Personal Information collected from children that we have actual knowledge are under the age of thirteen (13) to third parties, except in special cases where Snail USA has reason to believe that disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (whether intentionally or unintentionally) with Snail USA’s rights or property or anyone else who may be harmed by such actions, or if required by law.

Snail USA recommends that parents/guardians monitor and supervise the online activities of their children and to consider using available parental control tools which can prevent children from disclosing their name, address, and other Personal Information without parental permission. Visitors to the Web Site who are under thirteen (13) years old should not be submitting any Personal Information, such as their name, address, e-mail address, phone number, etc. without a parent's or guardian's permission.   

**Last updated: May 19, 2010**
